A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Council on the Environment, 1970-1988
Library of Virginia
- Series IV: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 29900], 1974-1977., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (20 boxes). (Box 1-20)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Section 401, Norfolk Applications, 1976 October-1977 February (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Section 401, Huntington District Applications, 1976 November-1977 February (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Section 401, Huntington District Applications, 1977 March-May (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Section 401, Norfolk Applications, 1976 December-1977 February (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Section 401, Norfolk Applications, 1977 March-May (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Coast Guard, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Dept. of the Army, Wilmington District, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Material sent to State Dept. of Health, Radiological Health, 1974 May-1977 December (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Dept. of Highways and Transportation, Inter-departmental memoranda, 1976 October-1977 May (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Dept. of Highways and Transportation, Inter-departmental memoranda, 1977 June-December (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Section 401, Nashville District Applications, 1976 May-August (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Section 401, Nashville District Applications, 1976 September-October (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Section 401, Nashville District Applications, 1976 November-1977 January (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Section 401, Nashville District Applications, 1977 January-April (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Water Conservation Act of 1976, Brion-Jensen report, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Water Resource Management Research Center, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Water Resource Management background, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Water Resource Management, Rural Water and Waste Task Force, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Water Resource Management, Requests for information and interviews, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Water Resource Management, Public's responses, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Water Resource Management, Interviews with Agencies and Organizations, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Water Resource Management, Outcome of Interviews, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Water Resource Management, Report, Preliminary drafts, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Water Resource Management, Report, Circulated draft, 1976 October (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Water Resource Management, Report, Requests for comments on draft, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Water Resource Management, Report, Comments on draft, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Reader's files, 1976 January (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
  - Reader's files, 1976 February (Box 15, Folder 5-7)
  - Reader's files, 1976 February (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Reader's files, 1976 March (Box 16, Folder 2-5)
  - Reader's files, 1976 April (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
  - Reader's files, 1976 April (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Reader's files, 1976 May (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
  - Reader's files, 1976 June (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
  - Reader's files, 1976 June (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Reader's files, 1976 July (Box 18, Folder 2-4)
  - Reader's files, 1976 August (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
  - Reader's files, 1976 August (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Reader's files, 1976 September (Box 19, Folder 2-5)
  - Reader's files, 1976 October (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - Reader's files, 1976 October (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Reader's files, 1976 November (Box 20, Folder 2-4)
  - Reader's files, 1976 December (Box 20, Folder 5-7)
- Series V: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 30902], 1971-1980., Extent: 21 cu. ft. (21 boxes). (Box 1-21)
  - Meetings (Transportation Hazardous materials, Water quality, Pipeline corridor), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clean Community System meeting, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Water Resource Management, Requests for reports, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dept. Highway and Transportation, Exemption background information, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Wisconsin, Environmental information, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Maine, Environmental information, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Florida, Environmental information, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut, Environmental information, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts, Environmental information, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Maryland, Environmental information, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minnesota, Environmental information, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Water Resource Management, Misc. background reports, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Southeast Basins Inter-Agency Committee (SEBIAC), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Water Resource Management, JLARC preliminary report, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Keep American Beautiful, Bulletin and report, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - EPA, Atomic Energy, General policy for licensing of facilities, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Guidebook for consultant services, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Environmental Impact Statement procedures, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Litter control, Nationwide, Background materials, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 19-22)
  - Litter control, Virginia, Background materials, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
  - Consultants - Environment and Technology Assessments, Inc., 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Consultants - Woodward-Clyde Consultants, Brochure, ca. 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Consultants - Institute of Transportation and Regional Planning, Brochure, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Consultants - Blaser, Zeni & Co., Brochure, ca. 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Consultants - Martin Associates, Brochure, ca. 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Consultants - Enviro-Pact Division, Qualification statement, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Consultants - Commonwealth Weather Service, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Consultants - Beak Consultants Incorporated, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Forms of Intent (Environmental Impact Statements to Council), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Forms of Intent (Environmental Impact Statements to Council), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Forms of Intent (Environmental Impact Statements to Council), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Forms of Intent (Environmental Impact Statements to Council), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Forms of Intent (Environmental Impact Statements to Council), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - EIS (Environmental Impact Reports) articles of interest, 1970-1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers), Norfolk District Permits, 1977 May-December (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers), Norfolk District Applications, 1977 May-December (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers), Huntington District Misc., 1977 May-December (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers), Wilmington District Misc., 1977 May-June (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Coast Guard, Notices, 1977 May-September (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers), Baltimore District Applications, 1977 May-December (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers), Misc. correspondence, 1977 April-September (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers), Public Notices-Norfolk, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Interbasin transfer, Water Resource Management by Dr. Allen A. Hoffman, Draft report, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Interbasin transfer, Water Resource Management by Dr. Allen A. Hoffman, Original, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Interbasin transfer, Water Resource Management by Dr. Allen A. Hoffman, Background (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Interbasin transfer, Background, Groundwater, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Interbasin transfer, Background, Legal issues, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Interbasin transfer, Background, Planning efforts, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Interbasin transfer, Background, Land application, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Interbasin transfer, Background, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Interbasin transfer, Working drafts, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Reader's file, Reginald F. Wallace (Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator), 1977 January (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Reader's file, Nancy F. McCandlish, 1977 January (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy (Chairman and Administrator), 1977 January (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1977 January (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Reader's file, Reginald F. Wallace (Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator), 1977 February (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1977 February (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Reader's file, Nancy F. McCandlish, 1977 February (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy (Chairman and Administrator), 1977 February (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1977 March (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy (Chairman and Administrator), 1977 March (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Reader's file, Reginald F. Wallace (Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator), 1977 March (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Reader's file, Nancy F. McCandlish, 1977 March (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Reader's file, Nancy F. McCandlish, 1977 April (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1977 April (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy (Chairman and Administrator), 1977 April (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Reader's file, Reginald F. Wallace (Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator), 1977 April (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1977 May (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Reader's file, Reginald F. Wallace (Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator), 1977 May (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy (Chairman and Administrator), 1977 May (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Reader's file, Nancy F. McCandlish, 1977 May (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1977 June (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Reader's file, Reginald F. Wallace (Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator), 1977 June (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
  - Reader's file, Reginald F. Wallace (Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator), 1977 July (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1977 July (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Reader's file, MRC, 1977 July (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1977 August (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Reader's file, Reginald F. Wallace (Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator), 1977 August (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Reader's file, Morse, G.C., 1977 August (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Reader's file, MRC, 1977 August (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Reader's file, Morse, G.C., 1977 September (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Reader's file, Reginald F. Wallace (Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator), 1977 September (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1977 September (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Reader's file, MRC, 1977 September (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Reader's file, Reginald F. Wallace (Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator), 1977 October (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1977 October (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - The Wives of State Officials By-Laws and Constitution, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bourassa, Col. J. Leo, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Walker, Fred W., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - General legislation, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - House of Delegates correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Senate correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly worksheets, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Legislative forms, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bills passed, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Possible nuclear waste repository, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Legislative correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Secretary Earl J. Shiflet, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Secretary Earl J. Shiflet, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Secretary Earl J. Shiflet, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - House of Delegates correspondence, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Senate correspondence, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - General Assembly worksheets, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Legislative forms, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - General legislation, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Reader's files, 1977 November (Box 5, Folder 20-22)
  - Reader's files, 1977 December (Box 5, Folder 23-25)
  - Monthly activity reports, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stream channelization, 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Local Environmental Management Conference, Questionnaires, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Local Environmental Management Conference, Speeches, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Local Environmental Management Conference, Follow-up, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Local Environmental Management Conference, Presentations, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1976 September (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1976 May (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1976 March (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1976 January (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Office of Commerce and Resources Meeting, 1976 March (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Office of Commerce and Resources Meeting, 1976 September (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Office of Commerce and Resources Meeting, 1976 November (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Legislative correspondence, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - General legislation, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - House of Delegates correspondence, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Senate correspondence, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - General Assembly worksheets, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Legislative forms, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Bills passed, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Bills P.B.I., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Bills held over, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Legislative correspondence, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Office of Commerce and Resources Meeting, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Office of Commerce and Resources Meeting, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Governor Mills E. Godwin, Jr., Executive orders, 1974-1976 (Box 6a, Folder 1)
  - Population statistics, 1971-1972 (Box 6a, Folder 2)
  - Local Environmental Management Conference, Working papers, 1976 November (Box 6a, Folder 3)
  - Local Environmental Management Conference, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 6a, Folder 4)
  - Local Environmental Management Conference, Biographies, 1976 (Box 6a, Folder 5)
  - Bemiss, Fitzgerald, 1971-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Green, Henry C., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Mattson, Axel, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Millard, B. Rice, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Montgomery, Dorothy, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Planning and Community Affairs, General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Planning and Community Affairs, General Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Planning and Community Affairs, General Correspondence, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Planning and Community Affairs, List of officials, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Planning and Community Affairs, Planning Committee, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Braun, Warren L., 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Weaver, Ralph, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Public hearing, 1977 Fall (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Public hearing, Working papers, 1977 Fall (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Proposed West Virginia Surface Mining Reclamation Regulations, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Environmental management in Virginia, Report by the Mitre Corp., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Governor's secretaries, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Whitham, Wayne, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Rowe, Maurice B. (Sec. of Administration and Finance), 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Speeches, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Speeches, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Speeches, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Speeches, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Press, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Press releases, 1971-1976 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Bills passed, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 26-27)
  - Correspondence, Misc., 1976 January-March (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Misc., 1976 April-June (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Misc., 1976 July-September (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Misc., 1976 October-December (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Shiflet, Earl J. (Secretary of Commerce and Resources), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Bills P.B.I., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Bills P.B.I., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Legislative correspondence, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - General legislation, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - House of Delegates correspondence, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Senate correspondence, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Work sheets, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Legislative forms, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - House of Delegates documents, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Senate documents, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Federal Power Commission, Byllesby and Buck Project on New River (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Dept. of Transportation Federal Highway Administration, Interstate 595 - Arlington County, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Dept. of Transportation Federal Highway Administration, Interstate 66 - Fairfax - Arlington County (Box 8, Folder 18-19)
  - Dept. of Transportation Federal Highway Administration, Route 58 - Mecklenburg County, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Federal Power Commission, Consolidated System LNG Company, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Federal Power Commission, East Tennessee Natural Gas Company, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Federal Power Commission, Blue Ridge Project, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 23-25)
  - Virginia Dept. of Highways, Route 262, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Dept. of Transportation, U.S. Coast Guard, Public Notices, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Dept. of Transportation, Transportation Improvement Act, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Virginia House of Representatives, Bill No. 7970, Designation of Wilderness, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Virginia Citizens Planning Association Conference, 1978 May (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Land Use Issues Conference, 1974 May (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Energy Office, OCS Procedures and regulations, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, CETA Youth Employment and Demonstration Projects Act, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Public hearings, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 5-25)
  - Council member correspondence, 1977 December-1978 December (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Council member correspondence, 1977 November (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Council member correspondence, 1977 July-October (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Council member correspondence, 1973 March-1977 June (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1978 September (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1978 July (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1978 April (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1978 February (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1977 November (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1977 October (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1977 September (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1977 June (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1977 March (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Reader's files, Susan T. Wilburn, 1978 January (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Reader's files, Susan T. Wilburn, 1978 February (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
  - Reader's files, Susan T. Wilburn, 1978 March (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
  - Reader's files, Susan T. Wilburn, 1978 April (Box 10, Folder 7-9)
  - Reader's files, Keith J. Buttleman, 1978 April (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Reader's files, Susan T. Wilburn, 1978 May (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Reader's files, 1978 May (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
  - Reader's files, J.B. Jackson, 1978 June (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
  - Reader's files, 1978 June (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Reader's files, J.B. Jackson, 1978 July (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Reader's files, 1978 July (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Reader's files, 1978 August (Box 10, Folder 18-19)
  - Reader's files, 1978 September (Box 10, Folder 20-21)
  - Monthly activity reports, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Annual report, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Highway and Transportation, Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Reader's files, 1978 January (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
  - Reader's files, 1978 February (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - Reader's files, 1978 March (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
  - Reader's files, 1978 April (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
  - Reader's files, 1978 May (Box 11, Folder 12-13)
  - Reader's files, 1978 June (Box 11, Folder 14-15)
  - Reader's files, 1978 July (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
  - Reader's files, 1978 August (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
  - Reader's files, 1978 September (Box 11, Folder 20-22)
  - Reader's files, 1978 October (Box 11, Folder 23-24)
  - Reader's files, 1978 November (Box 11, Folder 25-28)
  - Reader's files, 1978 December (Box 11, Folder 29-31)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, General correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, General correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, Dept. of Interior, Advisory Board, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, Dept. of Interior, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, Coordinator's correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, Distribution, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, MAGCRC (Mid-Atlantic Governor's Resources Advisory Meeting) Conference, 1975 July (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, Bureau of Land Management meeting, 1975 May (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, Dept. of the Interior meeting, 1975 May (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, Committee structure, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, Governor's meeting, 1975 January (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - State Governmental Management Study Commission presentation, 1976 August (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
  - Solid Waste Study Commission, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Solid Waste Study Commission, Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Recycling, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Solid Waste Disposal, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Arts Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Legislative tracking system, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Proposed federal legislation of interest, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - U.S. House of Representatives, S. 1865, Environmental Centers, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Federal legislation, Follow up, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - The Nature Conservancy, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Agency head - Board Chairman Meeting, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Strategic Petroleum Reserve Informational meeting, 1977 November (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Strip mining operations visit in Southwest Virginia, 1977 November (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Outer Continental Shelf, Bureau of Land Management correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Symposium - Public policy and historic preservation, 1977 September (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Misc. correspondence, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Resource Conservation and Recovery Act meeting, 1977 June (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - NAEP (National Association of Environmental Professional's) seminar, 1977 February (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - The American Assembly- Nuclear Energy meeting, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Appomattox River Scenic River study, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Catoctin Creek study liaison, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Radiation emergency plans, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Energy, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Permit Coordination Task Force, Environmental regulatory process for consideration of Council members, 1977 June (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Permit Coordination Task Force, Mailing list, undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Permit Coordination Task Force, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 41)